《烈探雷彻》前情提要
Previously on Reacher...
他说:“六千五 每手十万”
He said 650 at 100K each.
可能是六千五百万的转账 六千五百万的掩饰费
It could be a transfer of 65 million, a $65 million cover-up,
六千五百万的贿赂款
a $65 million bribe.
我们找到了一个嫌疑人
We got a suspect.
阿扎里马哈茂德
Azhari Mahmoud.
国际刑警组织 知道他是恐怖组织的武器经纪人
He's known to Interpol as a weapons broker for terrorist organizations.
“他如幽灵一般 任何地方都没有他的照片”
He's a ghost. No pictures of him anywhere.
如果这些是分数 那写下这些数字的人就太粗心了
If these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
每张纸上有26或27个数字列表
On each sheet there's 26 or 27 numerical tabulations.
真正的问题是 他们在算什么事的时间
So, the real question is what kind of somethings were they counting?
今晚你不必孤单
You don't have to be lonely tonight.
在大西洋城的时候 有杀手曾经想杀了我们
There were hit men who tried to kill us in Atlantic City.
他们失败了 但他们有一张 叫新时代的公司的停车证
They failed, but they had a parking pass for a company called New Age.
新时代是一家航空航天公司
New Age is an aerospace company.
我是马洛伯恩斯 新时代的运营总监
I'm Marlo Burns, New Age Director of Operations.
停车证被发给了 一个叫特雷弗萨罗皮安的男人
The parking pass was issued to a man named Trevor Saropian.
- 他的车在哪儿  - 我们决定把车带走
- Where's his car? - We decided to take it with us.
天啊 是斯旺
Holy shit. It's Swan.
他曾在新世纪工作
He was working at New Age
跟一直想杀了我们的这群人一起
with the people who've been trying to kill us.
餐厅
真棒 我们开车撞破窗户
Great. Well, we drove a car through a window
这样我就可以阅读 一位五年前在新时代
so that I could read workers comp pleadings
滑倒的秘书的工伤赔偿诉状了
for a secretary who slipped on New Age stairs five years ago.
真开心我们为此冒着坐牢的风险
So glad we risked prison for that.
是啊 我也一无所获 没有新线索
Yeah, I got nothing, too. No new information.
我倒是觉得我们发现了一些新线索
Well, I wouldn't say we haven't found any new information.
我们有三名特别调查员死亡
I mean, we've got three special investigators dead,
一名在逃
one in the wind,
而失踪的那位刚好在新时代工作过
and the one who's missing just happens to be the one who worked for New Age.
怎么了 总得有人说出来
What? Look, someone's got to say it.
斯旺是这些人的同事还是同谋
Was Swan working with these guys or with these guys?
斯旺是良民
Swan's not dirty.
- 我们都想相信他没... - 我了解斯旺 我们都了解
- Look, man, we all want to believe that he isn't... - I know Swan. We all do.
你觉得那一点可能性都没有吗
And you don't think there's even a chance...
绝不可能
No. I don't.
专注于我们的发现
Focus on what we found.
“布拉德”
Brad?
史黛西
Stacy?
我说的是这种“布拉德”
This is a brad.
那是紧固件 这么小的东西 居然有两个名字 太蠢了
That is a fastener. Two names for something that size is stupid.
这段对话也很蠢
So is this conversation.
说起名字
Well, speaking of names,
我刚在员工目录中 发现了我们的人的名字
just found our man in the employee directory.
看来斯旺的职位是安全总监助理
Seems Swan's title was assistant director of security.
“谢恩兰斯顿 安全总监”
Shane Langston, director of security.
也许在大西洋城 跟我通话的就是这个人
Maybe he's the guy I got on the phone in Atlantic City.
何出此言
Why would you say that?
他是安全部门的老大 负责发号施令
He's the security boss and bosses give orders
我们杀掉的那些人 接到命令要干掉我们
and the guys we killed had orders to take us out.
这只是推测 他可能是 让斯旺陷入这一切的罪魁祸首
Just a theory. He could be the guy that got Swan caught up in all this.
如果不是斯旺先让他卷进去的话
Well, if Swan didn't pull him into it first...
- 我已经跟你说了... - 你不是说假设害死人吗
I already told you... Aren't you the guy that said that assumptions kill?
你在假设斯旺 离开110小组后没有变化
Well, you're assuming that Swan's the same guy he was back in the 110.
嘿 这就是雷彻 在萨罗皮安家外面追的那个人
Hey, this is the guy Reacher chased down outside of Saropian's house.
跟他身份证的照片一致
Same photo as his ID badge.
副安全官员
Associate security officer.
真不错
Well, that's great.
斯旺 柯林斯
Swan, Collins,
两名新时代的安全部门人员与此有关
that's two New Age security personnel somehow involved in this.
- 现在我们得调查所有这些混蛋 - 别忘了马洛伯恩斯
Now we got to look into all these fuckers. Don't forget Marlo Burns.
是她置我们于险境 她给了我们萨罗皮安的地址
She knew she was sending us right into a buzzsaw when she gave us Saropian's address.
所以整个公司都很可疑
So, the entire company's suspect.
这个公司有一千多名员工 我们怎么查这么多人
We got over a thousand employees. How we gonna tackle that?
一次一个
One at a time.
烈探雷彻
第二季第四集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
纽约市
昨晚 你申请了 某国防公司的深夜搜查令
Last night you asked for a late night warrant for some defense firm,
而一个小时后 这地方就发生了入室盗窃
and an hour later, the place is hit with a smash-and-grab.
你知道这让我们看起来像什么吗
Okay, do you know how that makes this department look?
就好像我们步步落后一样
Like we're five steps behind everything.
我收集到了足够多的证据 才申请的搜查令
I made those applications when I had enough for a warrant.
而在你等待搜查令的时候 你本该从那里收集的证据
And while you were waiting for them, all the evidence that you would have collected
已经全部被带走了
from that place is all cleaned out.
我跟你打赌 就是那些
And I'll bet you that it is those tin soldiers
给你打出黑眼圈的破军人干的
that you were supposed to be keeping your black eye on.
不是那群军队混混干的 我跟他们说得很清楚
It wasn't the army brats. I made it crystal clear to them
- 让他们守规矩  - 我知道了
not to color outside the lines. Oh, I see.
你觉得你好好跟他们说话 他们就会配合
You thought, if you told them nicely, they'd play along?
你是纽约市警察局的
You're NYPD.
天啊 这些人都是他妈的私家侦探
These are fucking PIs, for Chrissakes.
这超出你的能力范围了吗 拉索
Is this too fucking much for you, Russo?
中尉 小声点
Lieutenant, lower your voice.
小声点
Lower my voice?
你让我在我自己的办公室里 讲话小声点
You're telling me to lower my voice in my own fucking office?
好吧
Okay.
请你去了解一下 他们都发现了什么 好吗
Would you please go and find out what they learned, all right?
我这么说话够客气了吧 拉索
Am I asking you nicely enough, Russo?
- 我会处理好的 - 很好
I'll get it handled. Great.
关门
Close the door.
谁放的这首歌
Who put this song on?
这是传声头像乐队的歌
This is the Talking Heads.
你跟传声头像乐队有仇吗  我们现在在纽约呢
You got beef with the Talking Heads? We're in New York.
他们是纽约的乐队
They're a New York band.
搬到了纽约的罗德岛乐队
They're a Rhode Island band that moved to New York
没 我跟他们没仇 只是
and no, I don't have a beef with them. It's just...
《此路不通》  刚好我们坐在这儿毫无进展
"Road to Nowhere," when we're sitting here getting nowhere,
貌似有点晦气
seems a little defeatist.
而且这不是他们最好的歌
Besides, it's not even their best song.
我更喜欢《变态杀手》
Probably prefer "Psycho Killer."
我可能找到线索了
Um, I might have something.
我一直在找U盘里 所有和斯旺有关的内容
I've been scrubbing the drives for everything Swan-related.
- 然后呢  - 我发现了一件反常的事
- And? - And I found an anomaly.
他是安全总监助理
He's the assistant director of security,
他所有的电子邮件 都抄送了他的上司兰斯顿
so all of his emails have Langston-- his boss--
以及其他六名安保人员
and a half-dozen other security personnel cc'd on them.
合情合理 他们是一个团队 得共享信息
Makes sense. I mean, they're a team. They share information.
但他没有分享一切
But he didn't share everything.
有几封邮件是斯旺 和我们的老朋友马洛伯恩斯的
There are multiple emails between Swan and our old friend Marlo Burns.
只有他们俩 没有抄送其他人
Just them. No one else copied.
是关于什么的
About what?
音乐 但又不全是
Music, but not really.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
他写道
He wrote,
“前几天我在听一张专辑
"I was listening to an album the other day,
“我觉得你可能会喜欢 吉米亨德里克斯的《大胆如爱》
thought you might like it. Jimi Hendrix, Bold as Love.
“第六首歌太赞了 听听看 告诉我你的想法”
The sixth song is amazing. Take a listen, tell me what you think."
斯旺很讨厌亨德里克斯 他讨厌任何吵闹的吉他曲...
Swan hated Hendrix. Anything with hard guitar.
不弹斯金纳德 齐柏林 亨德里克斯和谁人乐队的歌
No Skynyrd, no Hendrix, no Zeppelin, no Who.
- 这是他的原则 - 他没有让其他人看这封邮件
I mean, that was his rule. He's leaving everyone else off the email
而他在邮件里说他喜欢 我们知道他讨厌的东西
and saying he loved something we know he hated.
可能是暗号
Could be code.
或者也可能是春心萌动
Or it could be a guy trying to get laid.
我曾经跟一个女孩说 我喜欢乔治亚欧姬芙
I mean, I once told a girl I loved Georgia O'Keeffe.
我们会说这种话
We say things.
是的 我查到第六首歌叫《小翅膀》
Yeah. It says the sixth track is called "Little Wing."
等等
Hold on.
- 我说过你很聪明吗 内格利  - 还远远不够
I ever tell you you're smart, Neagley? Not nearly enough.
这里 这是一份联邦国防项目的文件 项目名叫“小翅膀”
Right here. A file on a federal defense project called Little Wing,
这是迄今为止 新时代签下的最大的合同
by far the biggest contract New Age has ever had.
是我在其他记录中见过的四倍
Four times the size of anything I've seen anywhere else in their records.
一份九位数的合同
A nine-figure contract.
人们为了更少的利益杀人
People have murdered for less.
看看这份办公室内部备忘录
Look at this interoffice memo.
他们似乎为一些军事要员 甚至包括一位参议员
Seems a test for the Little Wing tech was held for some military brass,
对小翅膀科技进行了测试
even a senator.
什么测试 在哪儿测的
But what kind of test? And where?
上面没写
Doesn't say,
但他们确实指出 参议员马尔科姆拉沃伊
but they do note that Senator Malcolm Lavoy
保证他会获得国会的选票 让小翅膀变成现实
assured he would do all he could to get the congressional votes to make Little Wing a reality.
我引用原文
And I quote,
“他完全相信我们 在新时代做的这项工作
"He fully believes in the work we're doing here at New Age
“并且会不惜一切代价帮助我们”
and will do whatever it takes to help us."
如果你给的钱够多 拉沃伊连《芝麻街》的史纳菲都信
Lavoy would fully believe in Snuffleupagus you pay him enough.
你知道这个人
You know this guy?
有所耳闻 在华盛顿特区 拉沃伊被称为“纸袋”
By reputation. In D.C., Lavoy's what's known as a paper bag.
他的政治方针和投票都飘忽不定
His politics and his vote go whichever way the wind's blowing.
众所周知 他会做见不得人的事
He's known to do some shady shit.
所以如果新时代能靠政府合同发财
So, if New Age stands to make a fortune on
而拉沃伊是他们在国会的拥护者
a government contract and Lavoy is his champion in Congress,
这就说明新时代 让拉沃伊的口袋装得满满的
it stands to reason New Age is the wind blowing Lavoy's bag.
这听起来不对
That sounds wrong.
所以 失踪且尚不清楚 是否是良民的斯旺
So, Swan, who's missing, maybe dirty, maybe not,
给之前想杀了我们的马洛伯恩斯
is code-texting Marlo Burns, who tried to have us killed
发了含有代码的邮件
about a program supported
其内容是关于 一个道德败坏的政客支持的项目
by an ethically-compromised politician.
我们得跟马尔科姆拉沃伊谈谈
We need talk to Malcolm Lavoy.
我们永远没法接近参议员 从他口中套话
We'll never get close enough to a senator to find out what he may or may not know.
我们不需要接近他 这些人 从来都不清楚自己在给什么投票
Oh, we don't need to. Those guys never even know what they're voting for.
一千页的法案 立法记录 他们不会读那些东西的
Thousand-page bills, the legislative record, they don't read that stuff.
他们只会按照被告知的方式投票 但他的立法主任
They just vote the way they're told to. But his legislative director--
实际上是他们制定并起草法案
they're the guys who actually craft and draft the laws,
这对我们有利 因为这些人没有安保人员
which is good for us because those guys have no security detail.
这些人为什么要跟我们说呢
Okay, but why would those people talk to us?
我可以让他们说话 让他们求着告诉我们他们知道的事
I can make it so they'll be begging to tell us what they know.
你有什么想跟我们分享的事情吗
Something you want to share with the class?
听着 华盛顿特区有很多有权势的人
Look, there's a lot of powerful people in D.C. with, uh...
都有见不得光的事
confidential problems.
主要是不大光彩 但是合法的
Mainly unsavory, but legal, things they do
是一些他们不愿公开的私人行为
in private that they'd rather not get made public.
我的工作就是 确保他们的私事永不见光
My job is to make sure that their personal business stays personal.
而知道秘密的人会保守住这些秘密
And the people who know secrets, they keep those secrets.
所以 你敲诈勒索
So, you blackmail?
我是激励他们
I incentivize.
听起来很不道德 奥唐纳
Sounds sleazy, O'D.
比不道德差那么一点
It's sleazy-adjacent.
嘿 我得付私立学校的学费 好吗
Hey, I got private school tuition to pay for, okay?
我从不违法
I never break the law.
我只是把事实摆在人们面前 让他们知道
I simply present the facts to people and let them know
如果他们做错了选择会发生什么
which way the river's gonna flow if they choose the wrong course of action.
给我十分钟打几个电话
You give me ten minutes to make some phone calls, I'll get
我会找到立法主任的名字 和他的致命弱点
the name of the legislative director and an Achilles' heel.
动手吧
Do it.
好的
All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道你不想说斯旺...
Reacher, I know you don't want to talk about Swan...
斯旺是清白的 如果他有问题 他不会像其他人一样消失
Swan's clean. If he wasn't, he wouldn't have disappeared like the rest of the guys.
但他并没有像其他人一样消失
But he didn't disappear like the rest of the guys.
他的尸体始终没被发现 他的家也没被毁
His body was never found His place wasn't trashed.
他不会就这么让他的狗渴死 斯旺不是那种人
He wouldn't just leave his dog to die. Not who Swan was.
也许吧
Maybe.
也许他迅速逃跑
Or maybe he ran off so fast
因为他知道三个愤怒的士兵 和一头怪兽会去找他
because he knew three pissed-off soldiers and a kaiju were coming for him.
狗受到了附带伤害
Dog was collateral damage.
好吧 听我说 我们不知道 110小组解散后 斯旺在忙什么
Okay, look, we don't know what Swan's been up to since the 110th ended.
他可能缺钱 可能收脏钱
Right? I mean, he could have money problems. He could have been taking payoffs.
如果有人告诉你我收脏钱 你会相信吗
Would you believe it if somebody told you I was taking payoffs?
不会
No.
我只是说
I'm just saying
也许我们不像 我们想象中那么了解某些人
maybe we don't know some people as well as we think we do.
我招募的托尼斯旺 绝对不可能参与此事
There's no way the Tony Swan I recruited is a part of this.
不说了
End of story.
你看到我们拿出军徽时 他们脸上的表情了吗
See the look on their faces when we whipped out our badges?
他们看起来像比尔马泽罗斯基
They looked like Ralph Terry
在第七场比赛中 打出本垒打时的拉夫尔特里
when Bill Mazeroski hit his game seven walk-off homer on him.
马泽罗斯基 新规矩 孩子
Mazeroski? New rule, kid,
你不能引用
you can't reference
你出生十多年前的人的例子
shit from more than a decade before you were born.
滚开 海盗
Go, Bucs.
我们就快结案了
We're so close to wrapping up this case I can taste it.
你觉得他们会给我们什么  表扬 升职
What do you think they're gonna give us-- Commendations, promotions?
听起来还不错
I like the sound of that.
就此打住 少校
Pump the brakes, Major.
还有一大堆工作要做呢
There's still a hell of a lot of work ahead.
还要逮捕更多人 要拆除基础设施
More arrests to be made. Infrastructure to dismantle.
调查跨越三大洲的 货机 吉普车 直升机网络
Whole networks of cargo planes, jeeps and helicopters across three continents.
老爷爷 庆祝胜利吧
Just take the W, Gramps.
不要辱骂长辈
Don't sass your elders.
就是 对他好点 他都不打瞌睡的
Yeah. Take it easy on him, guys. He hasn't had his nap yet.
好家伙 看来我们这里有象牙皂啊 雷彻
Damn. Looks like we got some Ivory Soap over here, Reacher.
什么意思
Meaning?
意思是 这玩意很纯 会漂起来
Meaning this shit's so pure it floats.
有多纯
How pure?
百分之九十九
Ninety-nine percent.
难怪到处都是迷上这玩意的孩子
No wonder kids are getting hooked on this shit left and right.
放松 体育迷们 不用站起来
At ease, sports fans, don't get up.
我听说就快结案了
I hear congratulations are in order.
卧底买卖收获颇丰啊
That's quite the buy 'n bust.
几公斤的毒品
Kilos of poison
还有几个被逮捕的毒贩
and a handful of scumbag dealers off the streets
向我们出卖他们的朋友
and ratting on their friends for us.
这些都是小鱼 我们很快就会钓到大鱼的
These are the small fish. We'll catch the sharks soon enough.
你开始查这事的时候 我怎么跟你说的
What did I tell you when you started this thing?
“这个案子会是个怪物 所以关门放狗”
This case is gonna be a monster. Unleash the hounds.
看来你做到了
Seems you did.
说到怪物
Speaking of monsters,
霍滕斯四世怎么样了
how's Hortense the Fourth?
二十个月前 已经进入可怕的两岁期了
20 months, already into his terrible twos.
显然 他是个神童
Apparently, he's a prodigy.
各位 干得好
Good work, everyone. Good work.
说起神童
Talking about a prodigy,
你就要达到百加得151里程碑了
you're about to hit your Bacardi milestone.
已经侦破151起案件了
151 cases closed.
在案子完成前 不要加到统计表里
Don't add it to the stats sheets till it's done.
我们这一行的人会被派往海外
People in our profession
在那里 我们会被枪击 被轰炸 被简易爆炸装置炸飞
are sent overseas where we're shot at, bombed, blasted from IEDs.
然后这些混蛋会靠卖这玩意
Then these assholes make more money selling this shit
赚的比我们所有人的养老金总和都多
than all our pensions combined.
真不公平
It's fucked up.
我就说说而已
All I'm saying.
对了 48公斤值多少钱
How much is 48 bricks worth, anyway?
47.
少了一公斤 是47公斤 不是48公斤
one's missing. There's 47, not 48.
在调查中 细节很重要
In an investigation, details matter.
海洛因的数量是个细节
Brick of heroin's a hell of a detail.
那不可能 我在销售点数过 是48公斤
That's impossible. I counted 48 at point of sale.
要么是你数错了 要么就是有人递错了
Either you miscounted or they palmed one back to short you.
不会 只有新手才会犯这种错误
No, no, no. You do shit like that, you're not in the game for long.
我知道我们 往斯旺的车里装了48公斤
I know we loaded 48 bricks into Swan's ride.
我们查查你的车
Let's check your car.
什么都没有
Nothing.
谜团解开了
Mystery solved.
肯定是我开车的时候掉到后面卡住了
Must have fallen back there when I was driving and gotten stuck.
因为这个失误 我猜今晚第一轮该我请客
Guess the first round's on me tonight for that fuckup.
掉了一公斤的海洛因 我得说应该请两轮
Losing a key of H, I'd say that's worth two rounds.
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
其实我都忘记这件事了 但这不支持你的论点
I'd actually forgotten about that, but it doesn't support your argument.
斯旺可能本来偷了毒品 而他只是惊慌失措 并将其归还
Swan could have been stealing drugs and just panicked and gave them back.
也许他后悔错过了这个赚大钱的机会
Maybe he regretted letting a chance at big money go by.
也许小翅膀项目来了
Maybe something like Little Wing came along
他不能再次错过赚钱的机会
and he couldn't pass up that kind of opportunity again.
有很多种可能 我的直觉告诉我他是个好人
That's a lot of maybes. My gut tells me he's a good man.
你的直觉以前从没出过错吗
Your gut's never been wrong before?
你知道我是怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
你希望斯旺是无辜的 因为是你招募他到110小组的
You want Swan to be innocent because you hired him into the 110th,
如果他参与此事 你会做一些蠢事
and if he's involved in something like this,
比如你会因为我们朋友的死而自责
you'd do something stupid like blame yourself for our friends' deaths.
而正如我所说 这样很蠢
Which, like I said, would be stupid.
我们看看奥唐纳发现了什么
Let's just see what O'Donnell found.
科罗拉多州丹佛
梅森先生 我是埃尔佐格比医生
- Mr. Mason? - Dr. Elzogby.
我看了你的病历 乍一看 我不得不说
So, I read your intake, and upon first glance, I got to say,
有几个问题
got a few questions.
我和所有人一样都喜欢钱 但你是个英俊的小伙子
Look, I like a payday as much as the next guy, but you're quite a handsome fella.
我不会告诉你该怎么过你的生活
Now, I'm not here to tell you how to live your life, but
但你真的想让我给你整个新面孔吗
are you really certain you want me to give you a new face?
从某种意义上来说
In a manner of speaking.
别挣扎
Don't struggle.
你是医生 你知道发生了什么
You're a doctor, you know what's happening.
你的气管被割破了
Your trachea is severed.
血液正在肺部 你快憋死了
Blood is entering your lungs, you're drowning,
你的大脑缺氧 神经系统停止工作
your brain is deprived of oxygen and your nervous system's shutting down.
所以现在你几乎看不到我
So, by now, you can barely see me
现在你还听不到我说话 而现在
and now you can't hear me and now...
你死了
...you're dead.
我要和你的秘书说句话
I'm just gonna go and have a word with your secretary.
曼努埃尔埃尔佐格比医生 整容手术
今天所有预约取消
汽车旅馆
丹尼尔博伊德 拉沃伊参议员的立法主任
Daniel Boyd, Senator Lavoy's legislative director.
被宠坏的蠢货 一辈子从没举起过
Spoiled dipshit who's never lifted anything heavier
任何比灰雁酒瓶更重的东西
than a Grey Goose bottle in his life.
以C+的成绩进入弗吉尼亚大学
C-plus student who got into UVA and Georgetown Law
和乔治敦法学院 这都多亏了他父母的关系
thanks to Mommy and Daddy's connections. Real party boy.
真正的派对男孩
Two dismissed DWIs in college.
大学期间两个被撤销的酒后驾车记录
法学院第二年 他被抓到嫖娼
Second year of law school, gets caught with a sex worker.
指控神秘消失
Charges mysteriously disappeared.
平均成绩2.3 直接进入私人律所
Took his 2.3 GPA straight into private practice.
而现在他负责起草 决定我们命运的法案
And now he drafts legislation that decides the fate of the free world,
让他的老板给符合最会讨好他的 游说者的利益的内容投票
telling his boss to vote on whatever benefits the lobbyists who wooed him best.
所以他含着金钥匙出生
So, he was born somewhere between third and home base
从没听说过“后果”这个词
and never heard the word "consequence."
你要用你那招 “比不道德差一点”的伎俩吗
You gonna pull a few moves from your sleazy-adjacent playbook?
我就是这么想的
That's the general idea.
博伊德今晚将在波士顿 参加通俗乐团的筹款活动
Boyd's gonna be in Boston tonight for a fundraiser event at the Pops.
我们可以设个局 轻易拿捏他
We'll set him up like a bowling pin.
- 怎么  - 你竟然接电话了
Yeah. You pick up the phone.
我还以为你开车闯进那栋办公楼时
I thought maybe you couldn't answer because you broke your hand
弄伤了手 所以没法接呢
when you drove the fucking car through the office building.
我根本没受伤
I didn't get hurt at all.
你觉得这很有趣吗
You think this is funny?
我跟你说了 “别再搞牛仔那套”
I told you no more cowboy shit.
那辆车属于他们的一名员工
The car belonged to one of their employees.
我是去还车的
I was returning it.
听我说 大聪明
Listen, wiseass, my boss
我的老大因为你们差点把我开除了
almost punched my ticket because of you.
也许那是件好事
Well, maybe that's a good thing
因为我小队的成员濒临死亡 而你什么都没做
'cause members of my unit are falling from the sky like raindrops and you haven't done shit.
嘿 我想知道 你们从新时代得到的所有线索
Hey, hey. I want everything you got on New Age.
- 明白吗  - 好的
- You understand? - Fine.
这就是我这次接电话的原因 我有理由跟你说话了
That's why I answered the phone this time. I actually have a reason to talk to you.
我会把他们的安保团队名单发给你
I'm gonna send you their security team roster.
查一下这些人有什么联系
Run background checks, see what connections these guys have.
等等 怎么 你觉得 我是来给你们做文书工作的
W... Wait, wait, wait. What do you think-- I'm here to do your clerical work?
是啊
Yup.
我们正忙着去波士顿
We're busy heading off to Boston.
波士顿有什么
What's in Boston?
交响乐
The symphony.
他妈的
Goddamn it.
但在我们去北边之前 迪克森和我应该去跟马洛伯恩斯谈谈
Before we head north, though, Dixon and I should go talk to Marlo Burns,
给她施点压
step on her neck a little bit.
网上有地址
Address is online.
- 这就是为何我不买房子 - 是啊 好借口
Right there is why I don't have a house. Yeah, that's the reason.
那么 我们干活的时候 你们要做什么
So, while we do all the work, what are you guys gonna do?
我们要去拿些毒品
Oh, we're gonna go score some drugs.
你们好啊
Howdy.
- 见鬼  - 警察
Oh, shit. Five-O! Five-O!
真没礼貌
Well, that's just rude.
你这周运气不好
This just ain't your week.
混蛋 找份新工作吧
Find a new line of work, asshole.
她有个孩子
She's got a kid.
室内安全
House clear.
已确认
Affirmative.
有什么有趣的发现吗
Anything interesting?
只有马洛留下的一些昂贵的珠宝
I mean, just some expensive jewelry Marlo left behind.
留下的
Left behind?
你觉得她跑了
Think she bugged out?
她从后门出去了 门都没锁
She exited out the back door without locking it,
衣服扔得到处都是 显然是匆忙打包的
clothes are all over, clearly packed in a hurry.
衣橱和橱柜是开着的
Closet and... cabinets are open.
她拿走了牙刷和牙膏
Well, she took her toothbrush and toothpaste.
绑匪通常不关心口腔卫生
Kidnappers don't care about oral hygiene.
简是个玩家
Jane's a gamer.
品味不错
Got good taste.
你可能想来看看这个
Uh, you might want to come and see this.
谁会逃跑的时候 不带上储备的现金啊
Who the hell goes on the lam and leaves their cash stash behind?
显然 马洛伯恩斯不会
Apparently, Marlo Burns.
确认一下 您预订了一辆凯迪拉克凯雷德
So, to confirm, you've reserved a Cadillac Escalade,
三天后返还到肯尼迪机场 对吗
to be returned within three days' time to JFK Airport.
科罗拉多州驾驶证 埃尔佐格比
没错
That's correct.
为了答谢老顾客
And to thank you for your loyalty,
我们免费给您升级到 SiriusXM白金聆听体验
we've upgraded you to a SiriusXM Platinum listening experience, free of charge.
太棒了
Wonderful.
谢谢惠顾 埃尔佐格比医生 祝您旅途愉快
Thank you for your business, Dr. Elzogby. Have a wonderful drive.
你想要这个吗
Would you like this?
你知道我为什么这么喜欢漫画书吗
Do you know why I love comic books so much?
马萨诸塞州波士顿
看看你
Well, look at you.
你不觉得现在更文明了吗 杜立特女士
Don't you feel more civilized now, Ms. Doolittle?
- 你之前穿的那身衣服在哪里  - 垃圾桶
Wait, where are the clothes you were wearing? Garbage.
垃圾桶 为什么
Garbage, why?
我已经提着靴子了
I'm already carrying boots.
如果我还有更多衣服的话 很快我就需要手提箱了
If I had any more clothes, pretty soon I'd need a suitcase.
要是我有了手提箱 我需要一个房子来存放它
I got a suitcase, I need a house to keep it in.
然后我还需要一辆车停在车道上
Then I need a car for the driveway.
很快 我就得填写各种表格
Before you know it, I'm filling out all kinds of forms.
所以 对你来说 一件备用衬衫太累赘了
So, a spare shirt's just too much of an attachment for you?
有人诊断说你是反社会人格吗
Anyone ever diagnose you as a sociopath?
诊断 没有
Diagnosed? No.
那么 你觉得马洛伯恩斯 为什么慌忙逃跑
So... what do you make of Marlo Burns taking off
只带了几件衣服 把所有现金都留下
with just some clothes and leaving all that cash behind?
我还不确定
Not sure yet.
她确实拿走了牙刷
Well, she did take her toothbrush.
她应该是你的灵魂伴侣吧
She could be your soul mate.
闭嘴
Shut up.
一个字都别说
Not one word.
- 天啊 - 那是两个字了
Holy shit. That's two words.
再说一个字 我就把这个小高跟插进你屁眼里
Another one, and I'll shove this kitten heel right up your ass.
我只是说你很漂亮 你们俩都看起来不错
I'm just saying you look nice. You both look nice.
我们看起来就像婚礼蛋糕上的混蛋
We look like the assholes on top of a wedding cake.
给 等我的养老金到账 我会在一个月内还给你的
Here, I'll pay you back in a month when my pension lands.
你的养老金可买不起那套西服
Yeah, your pension won't cover that suit.
也付不起酒店房间 机票也付不起
Or the hotel room. Or the plane ticket.
我会在两个月内还清
I'll pay you back in two months.
好的
Okay.
大家都准备好了吗
Everyone ready?
我们去听无聊的音乐吧
Let's go listen to some boring-ass music.
好的
Okay.
闭上嘴巴 老大 你的嘴巴大得都快进苍蝇了
And, uh, close your mouth, boss. You're catching flies.
借过
Excuse me.
谢谢 对不起
Thank you. Pardon me.
- 借过 - 没事
- Excuse me. - Of course. Okay.
不对 这...
Oh, no, it's...
- 抱歉 - 没事
Apologies. Not at all.
对不起 我有点晕头转向的 我不知道我的座位
I'm-I'm sorry. I'm a little turned around. I don't know if I have
是在乐队席还是在楼层包厢
orchestra seats or floor box seats,
我其实都不知道这是什么意思
and I actually don't even know what that means.
- 介意吗  - 我们看看票上写的什么
- Okay, well... - Do you mind? Let's just see what we got here.
- 夹层楼 那是你的位置... - 好的
Hmm, the mezzanine, that's where you are, but... Okay.
...但那座位可不怎么样 你会想坐在这里
that just simply won't cut it. You see, you want to be down here.
声音就像羊毛一样包围着你
The sound, it just wraps around you like a fleece.
等我的助手来了 你跟他换个位置吧
How about I swap your ticket with my aide when he arrives?
他不介意吗
Wouldn't he mind?
他要是想保住工作 就不会介意
Well, not if he wants to keep his job.
请坐吧
Please, take a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
稳操胜券
In the bag.
我们有13/14 8/13
We go 13/14s. 8/13s.
总共七个月 每周工作六天
Over seven months, six-day working weeks.
也许是一个记录时间的时间表  也许是一种评级标准 我不知道
Maybe a time sheet clocking hours? Maybe a ratings scale? I don't know.
需要加水吗
Top you off?
- 需要 - 需要 女士
Yeah. Yes, ma'am.
还有 请把账单拿给我 好吗  这家伙没钱
And when you get the chance, could you bring me the bill? This guy doesn't have any money.
当然可以 让我帮你统计一下
Sure. Let me tally it up for you.
太棒了
Great.
这是统计
It's a tally.
什么
What?
这里
Here.
13/14
13/14ths.
某件事发生了13次 但本来应该发生14次
Something happened 13 times when it was supposed to happen 14 times.
这里 11次的13次 8次的11次
Uh, here, 11 out of 13. Eight out of 11.
嘿 伙计 我只是...
Hey, bud, I just...
好的 我怎么跟你说的
Okay, what did I tell you?
手是用来帮忙的 不是用来打人的
Hands are for helping, not hitting.
向你的兄弟道歉 把你的乐高给他玩 好吗
Apologize to your brother. Share your Legos, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
我对你的爱可以往返月球
To the moon and back.
好的 再见了
Okay, bye for now.
对不起 我不知道 我为什么要给他们我的一次性手机号
Sorry, I don't know why I gave them my burner number, uh...
你看起来很开心
Well, you look happy.
我算了一下
I did the math.
有2197个事件 不管具体是什么事
There were 2,197 total events, whatever they were.
但只成功了1547次 但这个数字并不有趣
But they only succeeded 1,547 times. But that's not the interesting number.
看看他们有多少次 没得到他们想要的结果
Look how many times they didn't get the outcome they wanted.
2197减去1547
2,197 minus 1,547.
650天啊
Six hundred and fifty. Holy shit.
六千五 每手十万
Six fifty at 100K each.
这一切都以某种方式联系在一起
It's all connected somehow.
那么...
So...
那么 “手是用来帮忙的”
So... hands are for helping?
你口袋里还装着铜指虎
You have brass knuckles in your pocket.
我有《狗狗巡逻队》的创可贴 还有操场的沙子
I got a PAW Patrol Band-Aid and some playground sand, too.
听着 我不在的时候 他们不停地打电话 我...
Look, they call nonstop when I'm not there.
我在家的时候
And when I am there, it's, you know,
要早上7点去周末足球比赛
7:00 a.m. weekend soccer games,
参加教师会议
teacher conferences,
与妻子预订的做爱
scheduled sex with the wife.
我不再孑然一身
I am no longer my own man.
你不会拿它换世界上任何东西
And you wouldn't trade it for anything in the world.
六千五百万美元都不行
Not for $65 million.
你彻底变了 奥唐纳
You are a changed man, O'Donnell.
是啊 也许你应该试试
Yep. Maybe you should give it a go, huh?
买些土地 组建个家庭
Buy some land, start a family.
你会是亲师会上最可怕的人 但你会是个好爸爸
You'd be the scariest guy at PTA, but you'd be a good dad.
- 要是我有土地 我会有四... - 四五条狗
- If I had land, I'd get four or five... - Four or five dogs.
你会有四五条狗 没有女人
You'd get four or five dogs, no woman?
连迪克森都不要
Not even Dixon?
她是朋友
She's a friend.
好吧
Okay.
随你怎么说吧 就像是一件衣服
Whatever you say. That was some dress, though.
是一件很好的衣服
Hell of a dress.
是内格利的消息 现在是中场休息
From Neagley. It's intermission.
迪克森和博伊德现在要走了
Dixon and Boyd are leaving now.
他们在那里
There they are.
真是一件很好的衣服啊
That's one hell of a dress.
我的车在拐角处 那样可以吗
My car's around the corner. Does that work?
我会跟着你走 美女
I'll follow anywhere you lead, gorgeous.
- 我们去派对吧 - 好的
- Well, let's go party. - Okay.
看看她
Look at her.
博伊德没机会
Boyd didn't stand a chance.
又是内格利 她说我的人就位了
Neagley again. She says my guy's in place.
嘿 你的这位朋友会帮我们 对吧
Hey, this friend of yours. He's gonna come through for us, yeah?
如果他在军队的话 我会邀请他加入110小组
If he was in the Army, I'd have asked him to join the 110th.
过来
Come here.
你都兴奋了
Oh, you're all riled up.
我能说什么 古典音乐让我兴奋
Well, what can I say? Classical music gets my motor running.
慢一点 极速赛车手 我们先来点前戏
Yeah, well, drop it to second, Speed Racer. Let's have a little primer first.
你不是在胡闹 好吧
You're not messing around. All right.
- 好啦 好的 拿着这个 - 是的
- There we go. Ooh. Ooh. - Yeah. Yes.
拿着
Okay, hold this. Hold... hold that.
我一直不知道要弄多厚或者多薄...
I never know how thick or thin to make these things.
嘿 我来吧
Hey, allow me.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 女士优先
Okay. Ladies first?
不 你弄的 你应该得到奖励
Oh, no, you did the work, you get the reward.
恭敬不如从命
If you insist.
糟了 努力保持冷静
Shit. Shit. Just-just play it cool, just play it cool. Just play it cool.
先生 你得把毒品收起来 然后下车
Sir, you're gonna want to put the drugs away and step out of the car.
那不是我的毒品
They're not my drugs.
哪些毒品
Which drugs--
你化妆镜里的 还是你鼻子上的
the ones on your mirror or up your nose?
你觉得化妆镜是我的吗  全都是她的
You think I own a makeup mirror? They're all hers.
跟她说的不一样 而且她又没拿化妆镜
Not what she's saying, and she wasn't holding it.
她已经提出进行血检和尿检
And she already offered up blood and urine.
你想进行血检和尿检吗
Do you want to offer up blood and urine?
听我说 长官
Listen, Officer,
我不愿意这么说 但你知道我是谁吗
I hate putting it this way, but... do you know who I am?
我其实知道 博伊德先生
I do, actually, Mr. Boyd.
我还知道车里的那个女人 不是博伊德太太
And I know that woman in the car wasn't Mrs. Boyd.
我特别讨厌那些
And I have a special distaste for people
不珍惜神圣的婚姻的人
who don't appreciate the sanctity of marriage.
我也知道你是拉沃伊参议员的手下
I also know you work for Senator Lavoy.
但我在系统里查你的名字时
But when I ran your name in the system,
触发了当地联邦调查局的警报
it set off bells and whistles at the local FBI office.
他们派了几个人过来跟你聊聊
They sent a couple of their boys down here just to talk to you.
他们似乎并不在乎你的老板是谁
And it seems they don't care who your boss is.
我是杰克马格雷福特工
Special Agent Jack Margrave.
这是布雷克特工
This is Special Agent Blake.
我是奥斯卡芬雷中尉
Lieutenant Oscar Finlay.
律师不在场 我不会说话
Yeah, I'm not talking without my lawyer.
你想请律师吗
You want to lawyer up?
好的 给他打电话吧
Fine. Call them.
我会的 他们一小时内 就会把我弄出去
I will. And they'll have me out of here within the hour.
你知道
You know...
那就太晚了
...that's just gonna be too late.
因为等他们到这里时
Because by the time they get here,
我们就已经 在《环球报》和《先驱报》的头版
we'll already have the story of a senator's legislative director
刊登了一位参议员的立法主任
in the wrong woman's car with a snout full of booger sugar
坐在错误的女人的车里 鼻子里全是可卡因的报道
on the front page of the Globe and the Herald.
你知道
You see,
这不是大学或法学院 孩子
this is not college or law school, son.
你也不是被宠坏的 勉强拿到C+的富家子弟
You're not some spoiled rich kid barely rocking a C-plus.
你现在是个政客
You're a Beltway man now.
是人们喜欢搞垮的那种人
Kind of guy that people enjoy knocking down a peg or two.
所以这些指控
So these charges,
它们可不会逃过大众的法眼
they're not just gonna get swept under the rug.
我们不会让他们这样
We're not gonna let 'em.
想知道原因吗
Want to know why?
好吧 为什么
Okay. Why?
因为我们不喜欢你
'Cause we don't like you.
我甚至都不知道你们为什么来这里
I don't even know why you're here.
我们在这里是因为 我们想知道关于小翅膀计划的
We're here 'cause we want to know everything there is to know
所有信息
about Little Wing.
- 我也许应该... - 你应该
- I should probably... - Yeah, you should.
是啊 我要给 博伊德先生的妻子打电话
Yeah. I'm gonna call Mr. Boyd's wife.
她可能在华盛顿担心他
Eh, she's probably worried about him over in D.C.
非常担心
Worried sick.
老婆开心 生活舒心
You know, happy wife, happy life, huh?
好吧
Okay. Fine.
- 你好  - 我打错了
- Hello? - Wrong number.
说话
Talk.
这没什么大不了的
It's not that big of a deal.
小翅膀只是个代号
Little Wing is just a code name.
什么的代号
For what?
一项目前正在开发的新技术的代号
For a new technology currently in development.
一个令人难以置信的反导弹软件
Some incredible anti-missile software
它最初是为保护商用飞机而开发的
originally developed to protect commercial aircraft,
但某个航空公司找到了我们
but a certain aeronautics company approached us.
让我猜猜
Let me guess--
新时代
New Age?
是的 新时代
That's right. New Age.
他们发现该软件可以做些调整
They found the software could be tweaked.
它可以用于导弹中 而且不仅仅是针对它们
It could be used in missiles and not just against them.
它还可以缩小
It could be scaled down and installed
安装在便携式肩扛式地对空武器中
in portable shoulder-fired surface-to-air weaponry.
这个软件能让导弹击破
The software allows missiles
- 所有已知的对抗措施 - 怎么做到的
to defeat all known countermeasures. How?
那是穿着实验室制服的 书呆子才会问的问题
That's a question for a nerd in a lab coat, man.
好吧 我只知道
Okay? All I know is
从地面发射的导弹 能完全绕过它们的目标
that missiles shot from the ground completely bypass their target,
让飞行员相信威胁已经过去
making pilots believe the threat has passed,
然后它们重新校准 转身
and then they recalibrate, turn around,
重新瞄准飞机 重新进行攻击
zero back in on the aircraft and reattack.
这必死无疑 无法避免
It's death from above and there is no way to avoid it.
你开火 就能射中目标 就是这样
You fire, you hit your target. Period.
那拉沃伊参议员参与了什么
And what's Senator Lavoy's involvement?
项目需要一个拨款法案 好吗
Well, the project required an appropriation bill, all right?
你想要通过一个法案
You want to get one passed?
就得面对多年的繁文缛节
You're looking at years of bureaucratic bullshit
这都要归功于一些 关于修改民用技术的古怪法律
all thanks to some arcane laws on modifying civilian tech.
但拉沃伊知道小翅膀 会带领我们的军队走向未来
But Lavoy knew Little Wing would slingshot our military into the future,
所以如果我们袖手旁观
so if we just sat on our hands,
等待申请通过正规渠道
waiting for it to go through the proper channels,
那永远都无法落实
it would never happen.
所以我猜拉沃伊没有以最体面的方式
So I'm assuming Lavoy didn't clear up the red tape
清除繁文缛节
in the most reputable manner?
我帮忙把提案塞进了 一份一千页的法规中
I helped bury the proposal in a thousand-page statute
与此同时 拉沃伊负责握手拉选票
while Lavoy shook hands and drummed up votes.
甚至都没人知道法案里有这个
No one even knew it was in there.
他纯粹是好心做这事
And he did this out of the goodness of his heart?
为了保护民主
To protect democracy?
没有收红包之类的
No fat envelopes slipped inside newspapers on park benches?
成熟点 好吗
Grow the fuck up, okay?
这是华盛顿特区 这是办事的规矩
It's D.C. It's how shit gets done.
此外 拉沃伊知道小翅膀会拯救生命
Besides, Lavoy knew Little Wing would save lives.
我的意思是
I mean...
每个人都嘲笑星球大战的防御计划
everyone made fun of the Star Wars defense program,
但看看我们现在的处境
but, hey, look at where we are now.
每个人都想从空中发射炮弹
Everyone's trying to shoot projectiles out of the air.
小翅膀可以击中空中的任何物体
Little Wing can knock anything out of the sky.
任何物体
Anything?
比如商用飞机
Like commercial aircraft?
你开火 就能击中目标
You fire, you hit the target. You said so yourself.
- 你自己说的 - 对 但这是我们的技术 归我们所有
Yeah, but it's our tech. We have it.
其他人都无法得到它
Nobody else can get their hands on it.
你们想的那种事是不会发生的
Nothing like you're thinking is going to happen.
新时代非常安全 他们的两个场所都采用了
New Age is incredibly secure. Both of their facilities
- 最先进的... - 两个场所
- implement state-of-the-art... - Both facilities?
什么意思
What do you mean?
新时代有两个基地
New Age has two bases.
软件是在纽约开发的
Software made in New York,
硬件是在丹佛的制造工厂制造的
hardware at a manufacturing plant in Denver.
还有什么
What else can you tell us?
没了 我发誓我就知道这些
Nothing. That's all I know. I swear.
嘿 拉沃伊和我 我们走了捷径
Hey, Lavoy and me-- we-we cut some corners,
我们确实做了一些不该做的事
we did some stuff we should not have done,
但这都是为了让国防法案通过
but it was all to get a defense bill passed,
保护国家
protect the country.
那结果如何
How'd that work out?
嘿 抱歉 所以毒品指控会被撤销吗
Hey, excuse me. So, are the drug charges getting dropped or what?
我不知道 我不是警察
I don't know. I'm not a cop.
真意外 居然接到你的电话
Heck of a surprise getting a call from you.
听说你又戴上警徽了 真是太意外了
Hell of a surprise hearing you're wearing the badge again.
中尉 彼此彼此
Lieutenant, no less.
是啊 退休可不适合我
Yeah, well, retirement didn't suit me.
说起来 我看你还穿着呢子大衣
Speaking of suits, see you're still sporting the tweed.
一如既往的可靠 芬雷
Reliable as ever, Finlay.
你是说你自己吧
Speak for yourself.
我们初次见面时 你跟我说了什么
What was it you told me when we first met--
“麻烦似乎总是找上你”
trouble always seems to find you?
你杀了很多人吗
You kill a whole lot of people?
- 时不时 - 需要帮忙吗
Here and there. You need my help?
你已经帮我了
Already gave it.
你还在转那枚结婚戒指吗
You still spinning that wedding ring?
时不时 但感觉一天比一天好
Here and there. But feeling better every day.
- 狗呢  - 杰克很能吃
- And the dog? - Jack eats too much.
狗如其名
Just like his namesake.
今天 老大 汽车正在行驶 如果我不尽快脱掉这件紧身衣
Today, boss. Car's running, and if I don't get out of this straitjacket soon,
- 事情会变得很难看的 - 内格利
things are gonna get ugly. Neagley?
我都没认出你 看起来很美
Didn't recognize you. Looking good.
别多管闲事 补丁男
Mind your business, elbow patches.
你听到这位女士说的了
Hey, you heard the lady.
如果我20分钟内不让她穿上牛仔裤
If I don't have her in jeans in 20 minutes,
我就完蛋了
I'm done for.
回见 雷彻
See you around, Reacher.
回见 芬雷
See you around, Finlay.
所以小翅膀可能会铸就下一起911
So, Little Wing could be our next 9/11.
我们的指令是什么
What are our directives?
你和迪克森去丹佛
You and Dixon go to Denver.
小翅膀软件需要导弹硬件
The Little Wing software is useless without the missile hardware,
那是硬件的制造地
and that's where it's made.
也许你们可以干扰一下 以免导弹落入坏人之手
Maybe you can gum up the works, keep the missiles out of the wrong hands.
奥唐纳和我会去华盛顿特区
O'Donnell and I will head down to D.C.
我想去国土安全局 看看他们是否知道AM的事
Want to swing by Homeland, see what they know about A.M.
如果他的作案手法是将人扔出飞机 他们可能有些情报
If taking out airplanes is his M.O., they might have some intel on him.
我们要怎么做
How do you figure we're gonna do that?
你觉得我们就直接敲门说 “国防部能出来玩吗 ”
You think we're just gonna knock on the door and say, "Can the DoD come out and play?"
我兄弟在国土安全局工作
My brother worked for Homeland.
他的联系人能帮到我们
His contacts can help us.
对哦 乔最近过得怎么样
Oh, no shit. How's Joe doing these days?
他死了
He's dead.
我饿了 我们应该吃饭
I'm starving. We should eat.
牛排大师 新鲜食品餐厅及肉店
我有权用浴室 我得换衣服
Dibs on the bathroom. I need to get changed.
是吗 你要把这衣服扔进垃圾桶 就像这位反社会朋友一样吗
Yeah? You gonna throw it in the garbage like our sociopathic friend here?
不会 怎么 你想借
Oh, why, you want to borrow it?
是啊 我很喜欢
Oh, yeah. I got the ass for it.
我很讨厌破坏舞会之夜
Hate to ruin prom night,
但交出你们的枪
but hand over your guns.
你为什么觉得我们有枪
What makes you think we have guns?
有人跟我们说你们有枪 雷彻
We were told you'd be packing, Reacher.
他们还跟你说 今晚你会死吗
They also tell you you'd die tonight?
我会死 真搞笑
I'll die? That's funny.
没有枪 所以没有噪音
No guns, so no noise.
他们说你们很聪明
They said you were smart.
我要砍死你
I'm gonna cut you,
割了你
gut you
让你...
and leave you...
大家都还好吗
Everyone okay?
还好 会愈合的
Yeah. It'll heal.
不能更好了
Never better.
我的鞋坏了
Fucked up my shoes,
但我没事
but I'm fine.
嗯
Yeah.
不用你问出口 已经完事了
Before you ask if it's done, it is,
只是跟你希望的方式不同
just not in the way you hoped for.
你造成了很多复杂的问题
You're causing a very complex operation a lot of problems.
价值六千五百万美元 兰斯顿
Sixty-five million dollars worth, Langston?
我猜你就是兰斯顿吧
Assume that's who I'm talking to.
安保部老大
Head of security?
整件事的老大
Head of this whole thing?
也许我们一直在用 错误的方式处理此事 雷彻先生
Maybe we've been approaching this the wrong way, Mr. Reacher.
叫我雷彻
Just Reacher.
好吧 雷彻 不如我们做笔交易吧
Okay, Reacher. Why don't we make a deal?
你想要什么我都能给你
I have the means to give you anything you could ask for.
你想要什么
What is it that you want?
我想把你扔出直升机
I want to throw you out of a helicopter.
字幕翻译: 匡思颖
创意监督 朝思